donordrive.com 2012-11-15

# Privacy Policy - DonorDrive

### Privacy Policy

**Privacy and Security Policy**  
Global Cloud, Ltd. respects your privacy. This privacy and Security Policy ("Privacy Policy") explains the information gathering policy and security precautions of our websites, www.globalcloud.com, www.globalcloud.net and www.donordrive.com ("our websites").

**Your Privacy**  
Global Cloud, Ltd. respects its users fully and will not sell, rent or trade any personally identifiable information automatically collected by our websites (including your name, address, email address, or credit card information). This Privacy Policy is not intended to cover information collected by any third party website.

**Cookies, IP Address and other Information Collected Automatically**  
Our websites collect necessary technical information to allow you to access and interact with our web site. Global Cloud, Ltd. does not share this information with third parties.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Our Privacy Policy does not cover links to websites operated by third parties. Please review the privacy policy of each web site before you provide any personal information.

**Changes to our Policy**  
Our Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with the safest and most secure experience possible. Since technologies change, we reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of our Policy at any time without prior notice. Please periodically review our Policy for changes.

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**  
By using the Global Cloud, Ltd. website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. From time to time Global Cloud, Ltd. may make changes to our websites technology and this privacy policy, and your continued use of our websites shall be your agreement to these changes.

**Opt Out**  
If you do not wish to receive any further communications from Global Cloud, Ltd., there are two separate opt-out choices available to you: 1) follow the opt-out instructions on an incoming email or 2) call 1-866-244-0450.

**To Contact Us**  
If you have any questions, concerns or would like further clarification, please email us at info@globalcloud.net or write us: Privacy Policy, Global Cloud, Ltd., 30 West Third Street, Cincinnati, OH 45202.
